Getting a good grade from a subject,
대부분의 학생과 부모님들에게
is seen by most students and parents as the most easy
과목에서 좋은 점수를 받는 것은
and simple measure of results in school.
학교에서 가장 쉽고 간단한 결과의 수단으로 보여집니다
Now, how are classes graded at Bodwell?
그렇다면 보드웰에서의 수업은 어떻게 점수 매겨질까요?
Grades are in the form of an average percentage
점수는 평균 퍼센티지로 나오거나
ora letter grade.
문자로 표기됩니다
For example, a student getting 95 in Physics 11 is an A
예를 들어, 물리 11에서 95를 받은 학생은 A로 표기되는데
That shows a very high overall achievement by the student in Physics 11.
이는 학생이 물리 11에서 받은 높은 점수를 의미합니다
Then there are B, C, and Fail.
그러고 나서는 B, C, Fail 이 있습니다
What is the fuller meaning involved in the grade?
점수에 포함된 더 큰 의미는 무엇일까요?
In fact, how much a student understands, thinks, and uses knowledge in any subject
실은 학생이 얼마나 이해하고 생각하며 지식을 활용하는지는
is not told by just one letter grade of A or B or C.
단순히 A, B, C 문자로 말하기 힘듭니다
A master teacher uses many ways
선생님은 학생의 학습, 사고, 이해를
to observe, measure, and provide feedback
관찰하고 평가하며 피드백을 주는 등
on a student's learning, thinking, and understanding.
다양한 방법을 사용합니다
Mostly, a student learns and presents his learning by answering questions,
대부분 학생은 퀴즈, 테스트, 시험에서 구두로 또는 적힌
oral or written,
질문에 대답을 함으로써
in the form of quizzes, tests, and exams.
학습한 것을 보여줍니다
When these are the same across classes or schools.
이런 원리가 모든 학교 또는 수업 시간에
We use the term "Standardized Assessment".
‘표준 평가’라는 용어로 적용됩니다
A student also learns by discussing, arguing,
또한 학생은 토론, 주장
solving problems, designing and completing a project,
문제 풀이, 프로젝트를 통해 학습하고
and working with other students.
다른 학생들과 작업을 합니다
Good teachers observe all these actions
훌륭한 선생님은 이런 모든 행동을 관찰하고
and give students feedback to provoke further thinking and questioning.
학생에게 피드백을 주어서 더 깊은 사고 및 질문을 유도합니다
The teacher is measuring the student's learning
선생님은‘형성 절차’를 통해
Through a "Formative Process".
학생의 학습을 평가합니다
All performances combined into one, final grade.
모든 결과물은 하나의 최종 점수로 나옵니다
A final grade for a subject will mean
한 과목에서의 최종 점수는
combining all that a students learns from
학생이 퀴즈, 테스트, 시험
quizzes, tests, and exams
토론, 숙제, 그룹 프로젝트, 프레젠테이션에서
discussions, homework, group projects, and presentations.
학습한 모든 것의 종합입니다
What is a G.P.A.? - Grade Point Average
GPA란 무엇일까요?
Transcripts give a G.P.A.
성적표에는 GPA가 있는데
meaning that the letter grades are changed into points.
이는 문자 점수가 숫자로 전환된 것입니다
A is 4, B-3, C-2. D or "PASS" - 1, Fail is a 0.
A는 4, B는 3, C는 2, D 또는‘패스’는 1, Fail은 0
The in-betweens of A and B and C and D are a half point.
A,B,C,D 등의 중간은 0.5점입니다
All points of various subjects are added
다양한 과목의 모든 숫자가 더해져서
then divided by the number of subjects.
과목의 수로 나눠집니다
If you still have questions about grades and G.P.A.,
아직 점수나 GPA에 관해서 궁금하신 점이 있다면
Please speak to any teacher or counsellor.
선생님이나 카운셀러에게 문의해주세요